(Penny:)What is the truth?
(Sheldon:)My Mr. Spock doll came to me
in a dream and forced me to open it.
(Sheldon:)And when the toy broke,
l switched it for yours.
(Sheldon:)Later, he encouraged me to do
the right thing and I defied him.
(Sheldon:)And then I was attacked by a Gorn.
- Okay, that I believe.
- Mm.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, Penny,
l want you both to know...
(Sheldon:)...that I regret my actions
towards the two of you. That's a lie.
So is that one mine?
(Raj:)- Yes.
- Well, hand it over so I can open it.
(Penny:)Okay.
(Sheldon:)And, Leonard,
even though I don't have one anymore...
- ...l hope you have fun playing with it.
- That's a lie?
- A big, fat whopper.
- Yeah.
l hope it breaks.
(Raj:)This is a treat. What brings you guys by?
(Bernadette:)Raj, Howie told me what's going on
with you and Lakshmi.